Let's start talking about logistic regression.
让我们开始谈谈逻辑回归 (字幕整理：中国海洋大学 黄海广,haiguang2000@qq.com )
In this video, I'd like to
在这段视频中 我将要
show you the hypothesis representation, that
向你展示表征假设 也就是
is, what is the function
函数是什么
we're going to use to represent
我们要用代表
our hypothesis where we have a classification problem.
我们的假设 我们有一个分类问题
Earlier, we said that we
此前 我们说我们
would like our classifier to
希望我们分类器
output values that are between
的输出值在零和一之间
zero and one. So, we
因此 我们
like to come up with a
喜欢提出一个假设
hypothesis that satisfies this
来满足该性质
property, that these predictions are maybe between zero and one.
性质 这些估算也许在零和一之间
When we were using linear regression,
当我们使用线性回归的时候
this was the form of a
这是一种
hypothesis, where H of X
假设的形式 其中H的X
is theta transpose X.  For
是θ转换成X的 关于
logistic regression, I'm going
逻辑回归 我要去
to modify this a little
修改这一点
bit, and make the hypothesis
位 并假设
G of theta transpose X,
G的θ转换成X
where I'm going to define
我将定义
the function G as follows:
函数G如下：
G of Z if Z
G的z如果Z
is a real number is equal
是一个实数等于
to one over one plus
一分之一加
E to the negative Z. This
E的负Z.
called the sigmoid function
称为S形函数
or the logistic function.
或逻辑函数
And the term logistic function,
而长期的逻辑功能，
that's what give rise to the name logistic progression.
就是引起逻辑进程的名称
And, by the way, the terms
而且 顺便说一下 这个术语
sigmoid function and logistic
S型函数和逻辑
function are basically synonyms
函数基本上是同义词
and mean the same thing.
和意味着同样的事情
So the two terms are
因此 这两个术语是
basically interchangeable and either
基本上是可互换的 要么其他
term can be used to
术语可以用来
refer to this function
参阅此函数
G. And if we
G 如果我们
take these two equations, and
使这两个方程 并
put them together, then here's
把它们放在一起 那么这里
just an alternative way of
正好是一个替代
writing out the form of my hypothesis.
我的假设写出来的方式
I'm saying that H of x
我说H的x
is one over one plus
是一分之一加
E to the negative theta transpose
E的负θ转换
X, and all I've done is
X 我愿付出一切
I've taken the variable
我已经采取变量
Z, Z here's a
Z Z是一个
real number and plugged in
实数和插入
theta transpose X, so
θ转换X，所以
I end up with, you know, theta transpose
我最终 你知道 θ转换
X, in place of Z there.
X 在Z轴上
Lastly, let me show you where the sigmoid function looks like.
最后，来让我向你展示S型函数
We're going to plot it on this figure here.
我们要在这绘制这个图形
The sigmoid function, G of
S型函数 G的
Z, also called the logistic function, looks like this.
Z 也称为逻辑函数 看起来是这样的
It starts off near zero and
它开始接近零
then rises until it processes
然后上升 直到
0.5 at the origin and then it flattens out again like so.
0.5在原点 那么它再次变平了 像这样
So that's what the sigmoid function looks like.
所以S型函数看起来像
And you notice that the
而且你注意到
sigmoid function, well, it
S型函数 那么 它
asymptotes at one, and
在一个渐近线上
asymptotes at zero as
渐近于零
Z against the horizontal axis
?的水平轴
is Z. As Z goes to
为Z Z的
minus infinity, G of
负无穷大 G
Z approaches zero and as
的z接近零和
G of Z approaches infinity, G
G的?趋于无穷大时 G
of Z approaches 1, and
的z接近1
so because G of
因为G的
Z offers values that are
?值在
between 0 and 1 we
0和1之间 我们
also have that H of
也使得H的
X must be between 0 and 1.
X必须为0和1之间
Finally, given this hypothesis
最后 鉴于这一假说
representation, what we
表示 什么是我们
need to do, as before,
需要做的 因为在此之前
is fit the parameters theta to our data.
是适合我们的数据参数θ
So given a training set, we
所以一个训练集 我们
need to pick a value for
需要选择一个值
the parameters theta and this
参数θ和这个
hypothesis will then let us make predictions.
假设会让我们做出预测
We'll talk about a learning algorithm
稍后我们将谈论一个学习算法
later for fitting the parameters theta.
拟合参数θ
But first let's talk a
但是首先让我们讨论
bit about the interpretation of this model.
一下这个模型的解释
Here's how I'm going to
这就是我要
interpret the output of
解释的输出
my hypothesis H of
假说H的
X.  When my hypothesis
X 当我的假说
outputs some number, I am
输出一些数字 我
going to treat that number as
要把该数字的
the estimated probability that Y
概率估计Y
is equal to one on a
等于为一个在
new input example X. Here is what I mean.
新的输入例如X 这就是我的意思
Here is an example.
下面就是一个例子
Let's say we're using the tumor classification example.
比方说 我们正在使用的肿瘤分类的例子
So we may have a feature
因此我们可能有一个特点
vector X, which is this x01
向量X 这是这个X01
as always and then our
和平时一样 然后我们
one feature is the size of the tumor.
的一个特征是肿瘤的大小
Suppose I have a patient come
假设我有一个病人来了
in and, you know they have some
你知道他们有一些
tumor size and I
肿瘤大小和我
feed their feature vector X
给他们的特征向量X
into my hypothesis and suppose
到我的假设和假设
my hypothesis outputs the number 0.7.
我的假设输出数量0.7
I'm going to interpret
我将解释
my hypothesis as follows.
我的假设如下
I'm going to say that this
我要说 这个
hypothesis is telling me
假设告诉我
that for a patient with
对于一个患者
features X, the probability
的特征X，这个概率
that Y equals one is 0  .7.
对于Y是0 .7
In other words, I'm going
换句话说 我要去
to tell my patient that the
告诉我的病人这个
tumor, sadly, has
肿瘤 可悲的是 有
a 70% chance or a 0.7 chance of being malignant.
70％的可能性或0.7可能性是恶性
To write this out slightly more
要更加正式的写出来
formally or to write this
或写这在
out in math, I'm going to
数学 我要
interpret my hypothesis output
解释我的假设输出
as P of y
作为P的y
equals 1, given X
等于1 鉴于X
parametrized by theta.
参数化的θ
So, for those of you that are
因此 对于那些你
familiar with probability, this equation
熟悉概率 这个方程
might make sense, if you're a little less familiar
可能是有意义的 如果你有点不太熟悉
with probability, you know, here's
概率 要知道 这里是
how I read this expression, this
我怎么看这个表达式 这
is the probability that y is
是y的概率是
equals to one, given x
等于一 鉴于x
instead of given that my patient
而不是考虑我的病人
has, you know, features X.
你知道 假设X
Given my patient has a particular
鉴于我的病人有一个特别的
tumor size represented by my
肿瘤大小代表我的
features X, and this
假设X 这
probability is parametrized by theta.
参数化的概率θ
So I'm basically going to count
所以 我基本上要指望
on my hypothesis to give
我假设给
me estimates of the probability
我估计的概率
that Y is equal to 1.
Y是等于1
Now since this is a
现在 因为这是一个
classification task, we know
分类的任务 我们知道
that Y must be either zero or one, right?
Y必须是0或1 对不对？
Those are the only two values
这些是仅有的两个值
that Y could possibly take on,
可能是由Y呈现
either in the training set or
无论是在训练集或
for new patients that may walk
对于新患者可能
into my office or into the doctor's office in the future.
走进我的办公室 或在未来进入医生的办公室
So given H of X,
因此 鉴于H的X的
we can therefore compute the probability
因此 我们可以计算概率
that Y is equal to zero as well.
Y是也等于零的
Concretely, because Y must
具体地说 因为Y必须
be either zero or one,
是零或一
we know that the probability
我们知道的概率
of Y equals zero, plus the
Y等于零 加
probability of Y equals
Y的概率等于
one, must add up to one.
一 必须添加一个
This first equation looks a
这第一个方程看起来
little bit more complicated but it's
有点复杂 但
basically saying that probability of
基本上说这个概率
Y equals zero for a
Y等于零对于一个
particular patient with features x, and
特别的病人与特征x
you know, given our parameter's theta, plus the
你知道 鉴于我们的参数θ 加上
probability of Y equals one for
Y的概率等于一用于
that same patient which features x and you
同一个病人的特征x和你的
parameters theta must add
参数θ必须增加
up to one, if this equation
一个 如果该方程
looks a little bit complicated feel free
看起来有点复杂的感觉可以随时
to mentally imagine it without that X and theta.
想象它没有X和θ在脑子里
And this is just saying that
而这仅仅是说
the probability of Y equals zero plus
Y的概率等于零加
the probability of Y equals one must be equal to one.
Y的概率等于一必须是等于一
And we know this to be
我们知道这是
true because Y has to be either zero or one.
真正因为Y是零或一
And so the chance of Y
这样的机会对于Y称为
being zero plus the chance
零加的机会
that Y is one, you know, those two must add up to one.
Y是一 你知道 这两个必须添加到一
And so if you just
所以 如果你只是
take this term and move
把这个词和
it to the right-hand side, then
它移到右边 则
you end up with this equation
你结束了这个等式
that says probability Y equals zero
说概率y等于0
is one minus probability y equals
是一个负的概率y的得数
and thus if our
因此 如果我们
hypothesis if H of X
假设 如果H的X
gives us that term you can
为我们提供了这个词 你可以
therefore quite simply compute the
因此 很简单地计算
probability, or compute the
概率 或计算
estimated probability that Y
估计概率Y
is equal to zero as well.
是等于零
So you now know what
所以 你现在知道什么是
the hypothesis representation is for
假设表示为
logistic regression and we're seeing
逻辑回归和我们所看到的
what the mathematical formula is
数学公式是什么
defining the hypothesis for logistic regression.
定义逻辑回归的假设
In the next video, I'd like
在接下来的视频 我想
to try to give you
试着给你
better intuition about what the
更好的知识
hypothesis function looks like.
假设函数看起来像
And I want to tell
我想告诉
you something called the decision
你的一些被称为决定
boundary and we'll look
边界的东西和我们来看看
at some visualizations together to
在一些可视化
try to get a better sense
尝试 以获得更好的理解
of what this hypothesis function of
这是假设函数中
logistic regression really looks like.
逻辑回归应该有的样子